eglobalcentraluk.com 2019-06-30

# PRIVACY POLICY -

Last updated : 16th Oct 2018

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that eGlobal Central collects, and the ways in which eGlobal Central uses that personal information. 

**Personal information collection**

 eGlobal Central may collect, share and use the following kinds of personal information:

\- information about your use of this website (including to process the order and to deliver the goods ordered);

\- information that you provide for the purpose of registering for the website (including customer’s full name, physical address, email address);

\- information about transactions carried out over this website (including Credit Card payments unless using the PayPal gateway); and

\- information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including tailored product, promotion and terms and conditions updates);

\- information about the data during the use of internet at our server (including host name of the accessing computer, IP address and the time of the server request)

**Using personal information**

eGlobal Central may collect, share and use your personal information to

\- administer this website;

\- personalize the website for you;

\- personalize advertisement or other services, including advertising services for you;

\- enable your access to and use of the website services;

\- display information about you on the website;

\- deliver products that you purchase;

\- supply to you services and products that you purchase;

\- send you statements and invoices;

\- collect payments from you; and

\- send you marketing communications.

\- share marketing or remarketing insights with business partners including marketing agencies (i.e, Google, Google Adwords and Analytics tool), logistic company, payment gateway to personalize best marketing offers and shipping solutions for you.

**Securing your data**

eGlobal Central will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

All collected personal information is only stored for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected; and you reserved the right to request the personal data being collected, shared and used.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

**About cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user's computer through the user's web browser while the user is browsing. Cookies were designed to be a reliable mechanism for websites to remember stateful information or to record the user's browsing habits.

When seeking consent, you must agree our use of cookies for the website to analyse traffic data, usage statistics, and visitor’s behaviour. The purpose of using cookies is to provide a better shopping experience to the customer. You are able to decline cookies in your browser setting.

**Consent**

By accepting our Terms & Conditions, you agree and consent to eGlobal Central Privacy Policy and you are giving us permission to process your data specifically for the purpose listed above.

You may choose to revocate your consent on the collection or use of your personal information. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for the collection, sharing and use of the personal data for personalization of advertisement or other services purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing or emailing us. If you have any concerns, disagreement or complaints towards our privacy policy, you may also contact us with the below contact info.

Privacy Policy Supervisor:

eGlobal Central UK

Total Apex Services Unit 1001, 10/F

Mira Place Tower A, 132 Nathan Road,

Tsim Sha Tsui, Kowloon, Hong Kong

For all inquiries, please email support@eglobalcentraluk.com.

**To Unsubscribe**

To close an account, please visit our online support centre and submit a ticket. Your user account will be closed and all information removed from our server within 48 hours.

To opt-out from our newsletter subscription, please follow the instructions found at the bottom of the newsletter,or by this url link: _[UNSUBSCRIBE](https://eglobalcentraluk.us8.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=35bdafd6b4d69ac71632ed735&id=2cf6497227)_

To opt-out from our advertising or promotion information, you can unsubscribe and pressing the link "[UNSUBSCRIBE](http://www.eglobalcentraluk.com/unsubscribe.php)".

**Updating this statement**

eGlobal Central may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
